Guide to the Samuel P. Hays Post-World War II Radical Movements Publications Collection, 1915-1982 AIS.1981.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Radical Left Publications, 1949-1982; IV.
  - Aframerican Notes for You (Atlanta, GA: Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee), Nov. 1967, 8.
  - Aframerican Report (Atlanta, GA: Student Voice), v. 1, no. 2-3, 1967, 9.
  - Africa and the World (London, England), v. 5 no. 47, May 1969, 10.
  - African Opinion (New York, NY), v. 7 no. 1/2, June/July 1965; v. 8, May/June 1967 Jan./Feb. 1969; v. 9, May/June 1969-July/Aug. 1971; v. 10 no. 1/2, Dec. 1971/Jan. 1972, 11.
  - African Outlook: The Voice of Southern Africa (Pretoria, South Africa), v. 1 no. 1-2, July-Oct. 1967, 12.
  - Afros Expression: the Black Voice of Lake County (Waukegan, IL), No. 2, Sept. 1968, 13.
  - Albania Report (New York, NY: Albanian Affairs Study Group), v. 1 no. 1, 3-4, 8, Aug.-Dec., 1970, May 1971, 14.
  - All You Can Eat (New Brunswick, NJ), v. 1 no. 12, June 24, 1971, 15.
  - Ally, A Newspaper for Servicemen (Berkeley, CA), no. 1-29, Feb. 1968-Aug./Sept. 1970, 16.
  - Almighty Black P Stone (Chicago, IL), v. 1 no. 1-2, 5, May-June, Sept. 1969, 17.
  - Alternative (Bloomington, IN), v. 1 no. 4, Jan./Feb. 1968, 18.
  - Alternative From the Melting Pot of Dupage County (Naperville, IL), July 1968, 19.
  - American Dialog (New York, NY), v. 4 no. 1, Spring 1967; v. 5 no. 1-3, Spring 1968-Spring/Summer 1969; v. 6 no. 1, Autumn 1971; v. 7 no. 1-2, Winter-Spring 1972, 20.
  - Amnesty Action (Washington, DC: Amnesty International of the USA), March 1968; v. 2 no. 4, Dec. 1968/Jan. 1969, 21.
  - Anarchos (New York, NY: Eastside Anarchist Group), no. 1-3, Feb. 1968-Spring 1969; Special issue ("Listen, Marxist!"), May 1969, 22.
  - Anti-Apartheid News (London, England), May 1969, Nov. 1970, 23.
  - Anti-Imperialist Solidarity Bulletin (London, England), v. 2 no. 1, March 1969, 24.
  - Approach: the Mission/Education Newsweekly (Philadelphia, PA), v. 2 no. 12, May 6, 1968, 25.
  - Arrows (Sheffield, England: Sheffield University Union of Students), no. 97, 1969, 26.
  - Ascria Drums (Georgetown, Guyana), v. 1 no. 9, undated, 27.
  - Atheist (San Diego, CA), v. 54 no. 2, undated, 28.
  - Atlantis News (Saugerties, NY), 1 no. 1-6, Sept. 6-Nov. 15, 1968; v. 2 no. 7, April 4, 1969, 29.
  - Atlantis Quarterly (Glendale, CA), no. 1-2, Autumn 1968-Winter 1968/1969, 30.
  - Avalanche (Berkeley, CA), no. 5, Winter 1968/1969, 31.
  - Avatar (New York, NY), no. 1-6, March-July 1968, 1. (Box 80)
  - American Avatar (New York, NY), no. 7, Aug. 1968; 3rd Cycle, issue 1, Oct. 1968, 2.
  - Baltimore Defense Committee Newsletter (Baltimore, MD: Peace Action Center), Feb. 6, March, June 1, July 24, Sept. 12, Oct., Nov. 7, 1969, 3.
  - Baltimore Free Press (Baltimore, MD), v. 1 no. 4-5, Oct.-Nov. 1968, 4.
  - Baltimore Peace and Freedom News (Baltimore, MD), v. 1 no. 2-8, March/April-Aug. 1968, 5.
  - Banteng (London, England), v. 2 no. 1, Jan./March 1969, 6.
  - Between the Lines (Newtown, PA: Wells News Service), v. 19 no. 1, Jan. 1, 1960; v. 21 no. 7-8, 11, 16, April 1-15, June 1, Oct. 1, 1962; v. 23 no. 11, June 1, 1964; v. 25 no. 14, 18, Sept. 1, Nov. 1, 1966; v. 26 no. 2-3, 5-10, 12-13, 15-18, 21, Jan. 15-Feb. 1, March 1-May 15, July 1-Aug. 1, Sept. 15, Nov. 1, Dec. 15, 1967; v. 27, 1968; v. 28, no. 1-13, Jan. 1-Aug 1, 1969; v. 29-33, 1970-1974, 7.
  - Black and Red (Kalamazoo, MI), no. 1-6, Sept. 1968-Sept. 1969, 8.
  - Black Arts (Detroit, MI: Concept East Pub. Co.), v. 1 no. 3, Summer 1968, 9.
  - Black Bart: The Outlaw Magazine (Canyon, CA: Canyon Collective), no. 1, 3, Nov. 1971, April 1972, 10.
  - Black Dialogue Magazine (New York, NY), v. 4 no. 1-2, Spring 1969-Summer 1970, 11.
  - Black Dwarf (London, England: Socialist Review Pub. Co.), Special issue, Autumn 1968; v. 14 no. 17, 20-37, May, July 1969-Sept. 5, 1970, 12.
  - Black Lines (Pittsburgh, PA: University of Pittsburgh Dept. of Black Studies), v. 2 no. 2/3, Winter 1971/Spring 1972, 13.
  - Black Mask (New York, NY), no. 1-10, Nov. 1966-April/May 1968, 14.
  - Black Panther (San Francisco, CA: Black Panther Party Ministry of Information), v. 3 no. 21-32, Sept. 13-Nov. 29, 1969; v. 4 no. 1-30, Dec. 6, 1969-June 27, 1970; v. 5 no. 1-14, July 4-Oct. 3, 1970, 15.
  - Black Scholar (Sausalito, CA: The Black World Foundation), v. 1 no. 1-8, Nov. 1969-June 1970; v. 2 no. 1-2, Sept-Oct. 1970, 16.
  - Black Theatre (New York, NY: New Lafayette Theatre), no. 1-4, 1968, 17.
  - Black Vanguard (Danville, IL), no. 6, Oct. 1, 1968, 18.
  - Bond, The Servicemen's Newspaper (Berkeley, CA), v. 1 no. 1-11, June 23-Nov. 17, 1968; v. 2 no. 1-4, Jan. 28-April 14, 1968, 19.
  - Bring the Troops Home Now Newsletter (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 15-16, Oct. 17-Nov. 23, 1966, 20.
  - Buffalo Insighter ( Buffalo, NY), no. 2, 4-5, July 18, Sept. 25-Nov. 20, 1967, 21.
  - Bulletin of Concerned Asian Scholars (San Francisco, CA: Committee of Concerned Asian Scholars), v. 2, Fall 1970; v. 3 no. 1, 3/4, Winter/Spring, Summer/Fall 1971; v. 4 no. 1, Winter 1972; Special Issue: Vietnam, Feb. 1971, 1. (Box 81)
  - Bulletin of International Socialism (New York, NY: Workers League), v. 3 no. 1-24, Sept. 12, 1966-Aug. 28, 1967; v. 4-5, 1967/1968 -1968/1969; v. 6 no. 1-25, Sept. 1969-March 1970, 2.
  - Campaigner (New York, NY: National Caucus of Labor Committees), v. 1 no. 1-5, Feb.-Dec. 1968; v. 2 no. 1-3, April-Oct. 1969; v. 3 no. 1-2, Jan.-June 1970; v. 4 no. 1-2, Winter-Spring 1971, 3.
  - Canada Vietnam Newsletter (Toronto, Ont.), Aug. 1967, 4.
  - Canadian Dimension (Winnipeg, Man.), v. 5, Nov./Dec. 1968-Feb. 1969; v. 6, April/May 1969-April/May 1970; v. 7 no. 1-2, June/July 1970, 5.
  - Carta Editorial for the Informed/Interested in Mexican American Affairs (Los Angeles, CA), v. 5 no. 4-7, 11, April-July, Nov. 1968; v. 6, 1969, 6.
  - Catalyst (Buffalo, NY: SUNY Buffalo Sociology Club), Summer 1966; Spring 1969; Summer 1970, 7.
  - Catholic Radical (Milwaukee, WI: Catholic Worker Movement), v. 1 no. 3-4, 6-8, Nov. 1968-Aug. 1969; v. 2 no. 1-4, Oct. 1969-April 1970; v. 3 no. 1- 2, 1970, 8.
  - Catholic Worker (New York, NY: Catholic Worker Movement), v. 31 no. 11-12, June-Aug. 1965; v. 32, Sept. 1965/April 1966; v. 35 no. 1-2, 7-9, May-Dec. 1969; v. 36-44, 1970-1978; v. 45, Jan.-Feb., June-Dec 1979; v. 46, 1980; v. 47, Jan.-May 1981, 9.
  - Caw (New York, NY: Students for a Democratic Society), no. 1-3, Spring-Fall, 1968, 1. (Box 82)
  - Center Magazine (Santa Barbara, CA: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions), v. 1 no. 1, Oct./Nov. 1967, 2.
  - Challenge (London, England), n.s. no. 11, 1969, 3.
  - Challenge Desafio (New York, NY: Progressive Labor Party), v. 3 no. 9 Nov 1, 1966; v. 4 no. 3-12, June 1967-March 1968; v. 5, April 1968-March 1969; v. 6, April 1969-March 1970; v. 7 no. 1-3, April 1970-June 1970, 4.
  - Change in Higher Education (New York, NY), March/April-May/June, 1969, 5.
  - Chicago 15 Newsletter (Chicago, IL), March 1970, 6.
  - Chicano Student News (Los Angeles, CA), March 15, 1968, 7.
  - Civil Liberties (New York, NY: American Civil Liberties Union), no. 211, Nov. 1963, 8.
  - Clarity (New York, NY: Committee for Political Studies), v. 1-2 no. 4, 1968-Summer 1969, 9.
  - Comment, a Communist Weekly Review (London, England), v. 7, 1969, 10.
  - Commentary (New York, NY: American Jewish Committee), v. 43 no. 1, Jan. 1967, 11.
  - Committee to Support Middle East Liberation Newsletter (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 3-6, Feb.-Oct. 1969; v. 2 no. 1, Feb. 1970, 12.
  - Communist Affairs ( Los Angeles, CA: Research Institute on Communist Strategy and Propaganda, University of Southern California), v. 5 no. 1, Jan./Feb. 1967, 13.
  - Communist Comment (Cork, Ireland: Connolly Books for the Irish Communist Organization), no. 3, 5-6, 8-9, 13, 16, 28, 30-32, 1969-1971, 14.
  - Community Jobs (Washington, DC: Youth Project), v. 3 no. 7, July 15/Sept. 15, 1980; v. 4 no. 2-3, 5-10, March-Dec. 1981; v. 5 no. 1-2, 4-8, Jan.-Oct. 1982, 15.
  - Compass (Houston, TX), v.1 no. 3-10, July 1967-Feb. 1968; v. 2 no. 1-9, April 1968-Dec. 1968; v. 3 no. 1-7, Jan. 1969-July 1969, 16.
  - Communique for New Politics (Berkeley, CA: Community for New Politics), v. 1 no. 1-18, July 25 1966-June 19 1967; v. 2 no. 1-9, 11, July 31-Nov. 20 1967, Jan. 29, 1968, 17.
  - Con Safos (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 2-7, Fall 1968-1971, 1. (Box 83)
  - Connections (Madison, WI), v. 2, no. 10-14, May 1968-Sept. 1968; v. 3 no. 1-9, Sept. 1968-May 1969, 2.
  - Congressional Report (New York, NY: National Committee for an Effective Congress), v. 19 no. 1, Feb. 6, 1970, 3.
  - Consumers Voice (Philadelphia, PA: Consumers Education and Protective Association), v. 1 no. 1-2, Sept.-Oct. 1966; v. 2 no. 6-12, 1967; v. 3-5, 1968-1970, 4.
  - Crisis (Philadelphia, PA: Alliance for Housing, Jobs and Education), v. 1 no. 1-6, March-Sept. 1969, 5.
  - Crisis (New York, NY: Socialist Labor Committee), v. 1 no. 15, Nov. 8, 1971, 6.
  - Crusader (Havana, Cuba: Published by Robert F. Williams, in exile), v. 5, no. 4, May/June 1964, 7.
  - Czecho Cogito (London, England: Young Communist League), no. 6, undated, 8.
  - Democrate, organe officiel du nouveau Parti Democratique (Ottawa, Ont.), v. 1 no. 2-3, March-April 1964; v. 2 no. 2, undated, 9.
  - Deva (Birmingham, MI), v. 1, 1967, 10.
  - Direct Action (Voluntown, CT: New England Committee for Nonviolent Action), no. 66-97, Feb. 1966-April 1969, 11.
  - Dispatch (Washington, DC: News Service International), v. 1 no. 5-8, Feb.-June 1969; v. 2 no. 21-48, March 1-Dec. 8, 1971; v. 3 no. 1-6, 1972, 12.
  - Dissent (New York, NY: Dissent Publishing Association), Fall-Winter 1959, 1960-1964; Spring, Winter 1965; 1966-1967, 13.
  - Distant Drummer (Philadelphia, PA), v. 1 no. 2-11, 1967-1968, 14.
  - Douglaston Free Press (Douglaston, NY: Douglaston Center for a Democratic Society), v. 1 no. 1-5, July-Nov. 1968, 15.
  - Down Draft (Brooklyn, NY: Committee for Peace Organization), Jan., May, July 1964; Jan. 1965; Jan., June, Sept. 1966; Feb., Sept., Dec. 1967, 16.
  - Drums (Champaign-Urbana, IL: Champaign-Urbana Black Students Association), no. 7, undated, 17.
  - Daily World (New York, NY), v. 1, July 4, 1968-July 12, 1969, 1. (Box 84)
  - Daily World (New York, NY), v. 1, July 4, 1968-July 12, 1969 (Box 85)
  - Daily World (New York, NY), v. 1, July 4, 1968-July 12, 1969 (Box 86)
  - Economic Bulletin (London, England: Economic Committee of the Communist Party of Great Britain), n.s. no. 17-19, Jan.-July/Aug. 1969, 1. (Box 87)
  - Eldon Wildcat (Detroit, MI), no. 84, March 21, 1973, 2.
  - Eyewitness (New York, NY; San Francisco, CA), v. 1-2, 1969-1970; v. 3 no. 1-6, 1971, 3.
  - Fact (New York, NY), v. 1, no. 5, Sept./Oct. 1964, 4.
  - Facts (New York, NY: B'nai, B'rith Anti-Defamation League), v. 15 no. 2, Oct. 1963; v. 16 no. 1-3, 5, Jan.-May, Aug. 1965; v. 17 no. 1, Feb. 1966, 5.
  - Facts and Issues (Washington, DC: League of Women Voters), Nov.-Dec. 1965, 6.
  - Factotum Bulletin (San Antonio, TX: Center for Libertarian Studies), Dec. 20, 1968, 7.
  - Fellowship, The Magazine of the Fellowship of Reconciliation (New York, NY), v. 25 no. 22-23, Nov. 15-Dec. 1, 1959; v. 29 no. 23, Dec. 1, 1963; v. 30 no. 1, 3, 5-7, 9, 11, Jan., March, April-June, Sept., Nov. 1964; v. 31 no. 1, 3, 5, 7, 9, 11, Jan., March, May, July, Sept., Nov. 1965; v. 32 no. 1, 3, 5, 7, Jan., March, May, July 1966; v. 33 no. 7, July 1967, 8.
  - Fight Back! (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 1, Feb. 1968, 9.
  - Fight to Win (New York, NY: Worker-Student Alliance Caucus of Students for a Democratic Society), no. 1, 1969, 10.
  - Fighting Back: Political Prisoners Newsletter (New York, NY), no. 1, May 1, 1970, 11.
  - Fire! (Chicago, IL: Students for a Democratic Society), v. 1 no. 2, Nov. 21, 1969, 12.
  - Firing Line (Chicago, IL: Joint Community Union and the National Organizing Committee), v. 1 no. 7-14, Aug. 5, 1967-May 10, 1968, 13.
  - First Casualty (New York, NY: Vietnam Veterans Against the War), v. 1 no. 1-3, Aug.-Dec. 1971, 14.
  - Focus Midwest (St. Louis, MO), v. 4 no. 7-8, July/Aug. 1966, 15.
  - Forum: an International Socialist Discussion Bulletin (Berkeley, CA), v. 3 no. 3-4, Nov. 15, 1969-Jan. 23, 1970, 16.
  - Foundation Bulletin (New York, NY: Bertrand Russell Peace Foundation), v. 1 no. 8-13, March 15/April 1-June 1, 1967, 17.
  - Founders Record (Cincinnati. OH: Progressive National Baptist Convention), v. 1, March 1967, 18.
  - Fourth International, A Journal of International Marxism (London, England), v. 1, 1964/1965; v. 2 no. 1-2, Summer-Autumn 1965; v. 3, 1966; v. 4 no. 1-3, April-Nov. 1967; v. 5 no. 1, Feb. 1968, 19.
  - Free Campus News (Washington, DC), v. 1 no. 1-3, undated; v. 2 no. 12, undated, 20.
  - Free Student (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 2-4, Nov. 22, 1967-May 7, 1968, 21.
  - Freedom (New York, NY), v. 3 no. 1-8, 11, Jan.-Sept., Dec. 1953; v. 4 no. 1-5, Jan.-Aug. 1954; v. 5 no. 1-6, Jan.-July/Aug. 1955, 22.
  - Freedom: Anarchist Weekly (London, England), v. 30 no. 20-40, June 28-Dec. 20, 1969; v. 31 no. 1-16, 18-20, Jan. 10-May 23, June 13-27, 1970, 23.
  - Freedomways: A Quarterly Review of the Negro Freedom Movement (New York, NY), v. 3 no. 3, Summer 1963; v. 8 no. 2-4, Spring-Fall 1968; v. 9-10, 1969-1970; v. 11 no. 1-2, 1971, 24.
  - Freethinker (London, England), v. 89 no. 19-20, May 10-17, 1969, 25.
  - Frontier (Los Angeles, CA), v. 17 no. 12, Oct. 1966; v. 18 no. 1-4, Nov. 1966-Feb. 1967, 26.
  - Fuse (Oneonta, AL), v. 2 no. 1-3, Feb.-April, 1969; v. 3 no. 1, undated, 27.
  - Gallo (Denver, CO: The Crusade for Justice), v. 1 no. 1-14, June 1967-Oct. 1968; v. 2 no. 2-4, Dec. 1968-March 1969, 1. (Box 88)
  - Gary American (Gary, IN), v. 41 no. 32-34, 36-40, 42-47, 49-50, Aug. 9-16, Sept. 6-Oct. 4, Oct. 18, Nov. 22, Dec. 6-13, 1968, 2.
  - Gigline (El Paso, TX: Fort Bliss GIs for Peace), v. 1 no. 5, Dec. 1969, 3.
  - Global Digest (Hong Kong), v. 2, no. 8-18, May-Dec. 1965; v. 3, no. 1-10, Jan.-Oct. 1966, 4.
  - Gramma: Weekly Review (Havana, Cuba: Central Committee of the Communist Party of Cuba), v. 4 no. 44, Nov. 2, 1969, 5.
  - Grass Roots Forum (San Gabriel, CA), v. 2 no. 4-9, 12, June 22-Dec. 6, 1968, April 25, 1969; v. 3, May 30, 1969-July 15, 1970; v. 4 no. 1, Sept. 1, 1970, 6.
  - Greek Observer (London, England), no. 2, April 1969, 7.
  - Greek Report (London, England), April 1969, 8.
  - Green Revolution (Freeland, MD), v. 7 no. 12, Dec. 1969, 9.
  - Group Research Report (Washington, DC), v. 4 no. 1-9, July- Dec. 16, 1965; v. 5, 1966; v. 6, 1967 (lacks no. 22, Nov. 30); v. 7-8, 1968-1969; v. 9, Jan.-Nov. 25, 1970, 10.
  - Guardian: Independent Radical Weekly (New York: Weekly Guardian Associates), Feb. 10, 1968; Aug. 23, Oct. 4, Nov. 29, 1969, 11.
  - Guerrilla: Free Newspaper of the Streets (Detroit, MI: Center for Paleocybernetic Research), v. 2 no. 4, 1968, 12.
  - Hammer and Steel Newsletter (Boston, MA), 1966 no. 6-8, Oct.-Dec. 1966; 1967 no. 1-5, Jan.-Sept. 1967; 1968 no. 1-6, Jan.-Nov. 1968; 1969; 1970 no. 1-5, April-Dec.; 1972 no. 1-6, Jan.-Oct. 1972, 13.
  - Hard Times (Washington, DC), no. 22-87, March 10/17, 1969-June 29/July 6, 1970, 14.
  - Health/PAC Bulletin (New York, NY: Institute for Policy Studies), no. 1, June 1968; no. 9-14, May-Dec. 1969; no. 15-26, Jan.-Dec. 1970; no. 27-32, 34-37, Jan.-June, Oct.-Dec. 1971; no. 38-45, Feb.-Oct. 1972; no. 48-50, 52-53, Jan.-Sept. 1973; no. 56-57, 59-61, Jan.-Dec. 1974; no. 64-67, May-Dec. 1975; no. 68-73, Jan.-Dec. 1976; no. 74, Jan./Feb. 1977, 15.
  - Health Politics (New York, NY: New York University and the Committee on Health Politics), v. 5 no. 3-4, Spring-Summer 1975, 16.
  - High School Independent Press Service (New York, NY), no. 1-11, Sept. 1968-Feb. 10, 1969, 1. (Box 89)
  - High School Mobilizer to End the War in Vietnam (Detroit, MI), 1 issue, undated, 2.
  - Homefront (Washington, DC: Institute for American Democracy), v. 1-3, 1967-1969; v. 4 no. 1-9, Jan.-Oct. 1970; v. 5 no. 1-11, Jan.-Oct. 1971; Index: Jan.1967-March 1969; April 1969-June 1970, 3.
  - Humanist (London, England: Rationalist Press Association), May 1969, 4.
  - ISC New York: Fraction Reports, Minutes, Assorted Papers for Your Information (New York, NY: New York Independent Socialist Club), June 1969, 5.
  - IT, The International Times (London, England), no. 27, 29, 49, 51 55, March 8-21, April 19/May 2, 1968; Jan. 31-Feb. 13, Feb. 28/March 13; April 25/May 8, 1969, 6.
  - I. F. Stone's Weekly (Washington, DC), v. 9 no. 22, June 12, 1961; v. 10 no. 22-46, June-Dec. 1962; v. 11 no. 1-5, 17-25, Jan.-Feb., Sept.-Dec. 1963; v. 12-19, 1964-1971, 7.
  - I Kon (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 5-7, March 1968-Jan./Feb. 1969, 8.
  - Illustrated Paper (Mendocino, CA), Issue no. 9, Feb. 1969, 9.
  - In Search of a Relevant Progressivism (New York, NY), v. 3 no. 7-8, March 28-April 11, 1974, 10.
  - Independent Socialist (New York, NY: New York Independent Socialist Club), no. 1-12, Jan./Feb. 1967-Sept. 1969, 11.
  - International Socialist (New York, NY: New York Independent Socialist Club), no. 13-17, Oct. 1969-March 1970, 12.
  - Independent Socialist Bulletin ( New York, NY: Independent Socialist Clubs of America), no. 1-6, Jan.-June, 1969, 13.
  - Independent Socialist Newsletter (Berkeley, CA: Independent Socialist Committee), no. 2, March 1967, 14.
  - Independent Socialist Reports (New York, NY: Independent Socialist Clubs of America), v. 1 no. 1-2, Jan.-March 1969, 15.
  - Indochina Chronicle (Washington, DC: Indochina Resource Center), no. 1-17, July 15, 1971-July 1, 1972, 16.
  - Indonesian Tribune (Tirana, Albania), v. 1 no. 12, Oct. 1967, 17.
  - Industrial Worker (Chicago, IL: Industrial Workers of the World), v. 64 no. 27, 30-32, June, Sept.-Nov. 1967; v. 65-69, 1968-1972, 18.
  - In These Times (Chicago, IL: The Institute for Policy Studies), v. 1 no. 1-50, Nov. 15, 1976-Nov. 9, 1977; v. 2 no. 1-50, Nov. 16, 1977-Nov. 8, 1978 (lacks no. 7); v. 3 no. 1-50, Nov. 15, 1978-Oct. 31, 1979 (lacks no. 2, 17, 30); v. 4 no. 1-42, Nov. 7, 1979-Oct. 29, 1980; v. 5 no. 1-48, Nov. 5, 1980-Nov. 3, 1981 (lacks no. 8); v. 6 no. 1-42, Nov. 4, 1981-Nov. 9, 1982, 1. (Box 90)
  - In These Times (Chicago, IL: The Institute for Policy Studies), v. 1 no. 1-50, Nov. 15, 1976-Nov. 9, 1977; v. 2 no. 1-50, Nov. 16, 1977-Nov. 8, 1978 (lacks no. 7); v. 3 no. 1-50, Nov. 15, 1978-Oct. 31, 1979 (lacks no. 2, 17, 30); v. 4 no. 1-42, Nov. 7, 1979-Oct. 29, 1980; v. 5 no. 1-48, Nov. 5, 1980-Nov. 3, 1981 (lacks no. 8); v. 6 no. 1-42, Nov. 4, 1981-Nov. 9, 1982 (Box 91)
  - Inferno (San Antonio, TX), v. 1, 1967; v. 2 no. 1-3, Jan.-May 1968, 1. (Box 92)
  - Inner City Voice: Detroit's Black Community Newspaper (Detroit, MI), v. 1 no. 1-8, Oct. 1967-June 1968; v. 2 no. 3, 5, Feb., April 1970, 2.
  - Innovator (Los Angeles, CA: Forum for New Ideas), v. 2, Nov. 1964-Oct. 1965; Nov. 1965-May 1968; Autumn 1968-Autumn 1969, 3.
  - Liberal Innovator (Los Angeles, CA: Forum for New Ideas), v. 1 no. 1-9, Feb.-Oct. 1964, 4.
  - Inside Agitator (Chicago, IL: Chicago Area Draft Resisters), no. 1-2, ca. Sept.-Oct. 1967; no. 3-5, Dec. 1967- April/May, 1969, 5.
  - Inside Agitator (Bloomington, IN: Progressive Reform Party, Indiana University), no. 12, Feb. 24, 1968, 6.
  - Inside Eastside (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 13, May 13-26, 1968, 7.
  - Insight (Los Angeles, CA), v. 3 no. 1-2, June-Sept. 1967, 8.
  - Insight (Brighton, England: Students of the University of Sussex), no. 1-4, Spring 1968-Easter 1969, 9.
  - Intentional Community (Berkeley, CA: League for Community), No. 4, March 1968, 10.
  - Intercontinental Press (New York, NY), v. 6 no. 19-44, May 20-Dec. 23, 1968; v. 7, 1969; v. 8 no. 1-35, Jan. 12-Oct. 26, 1970; v. 9 no. 31, Sept. 13, 1971, 11.
  - Intercourse (New York, NY: Sexual Freedom League), no. 5, Oct. 1968, 12.
  - International Affairs Bulletin (London, England: Communist Party of Great Britain), v. 3 no. 5, March/April 1969; v. 4 no. 1-5, May/June 1968-Aug./Sept. 1970; v. 5 no. 1-5, Feb./March 1971-March/April 1972, 13.
  - International Afro-American Museum Newsletter (Detroit, MI: International Afro-American Museum Research Committee), v. 3 no. 1, Spring 1968, 14.
  - International Bulletin (Berkeley, CA: Internews), v. 2 no. 14-24, July-Dec. 1975; v. 3 no. 1-24, Jan.-Dec. 1976; v. 4 no. 1-24, Jan.-Dec. 1977; v. 5 no. 1-24, Jan.-Dec. 1978; v. 6 no. 1-16, Jan.-July, Sept. 1979, 15.
  - International Socialism (London, England), no. 15-28, Winter 1963/1964-Spring 1967; no. 36-44, April/May 1968-July/Aug. 1970, 1. (Box 93)
  - International Socialist Review (New York, NY), v. 28 no. 4-6, July-Dec. 1967; v. 29-30, 1968-1969; v. 31 no. 1-4, Jan.-June; v. 34 no. 11, Dec. 1973, 2.
  - Interracial Review (New York, NY: Catholic Interracial Council), v. 39 no. 7, July 1966, 3.
  - Irish Communist: Theoretical Journal of the Irish Communist Organization (Belfast, Northern Ireland), no. 41-65, April 1969-May 1971, 4.
  - Irish Democrat (London, England), no. 295, 297, 299-308, 310 312, March, May, July, 1969-April 1970, June-July 1970, 5.
  - Irish Socialist (Dublin, Ireland), no. 88-103, Aug. 1969-March 1971, 6.
  - Issue (Hartford, CT), no. 1-3, Winter-Summer 1967, 7.
  - Issues (New York, NY: American Council for Judaism), v. 12 no. 8, Winter 1958/1959; v. 17 no. 8, Winter 1963; v. 19 no. 1, 3, Spring, Autumn 1965; v. 20 no. 1, 4, Spring 1966, Winter 1966/1967; v. 21 no. 1, Spring 1967; v. 21 no. 4/v. 22 no. 1, Winter 1967/Spring 1968, 8.
  - Jewish Liberation Journal (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 4, Oct. 1969, 9.
  - Journal of Black Poetry (San Francisco, CA), v. 1, no. 6-13, Fall 1967-Winter/Spring 1970, 10.
  - Just Economics (Washington, DC: Movement for Economic Justice Education and Training Center and the Institute for Social Justice), v. 1 no. 2-3, Nov.-Dec. 1973; v. 2-4, 1974-1976; v. 5 no. 1-8, Jan.-Nov. 1977; v. 6 no. 1-2, 4-7, Jan.-April, July/Aug.-Oct./Dec. 1978; v. 7 no. 1-2, 4, Feb.-May, Nov. 1979; v. 8, 1980, 11.
  - Kandide: A Journal of Kansas New Left Thought (Lawrence, KS: Kansas Students for a Democratic Society), no. 1-3, undated, 12.
  - Kansas University Students for a Democratic Society Journal (Lawrence, KS), no. 3, May 1966, 13.
  - Katallagete: Be Reconciled (Nashville, TN: Committee of Southern Churchmen), Spring 1968, 14.
  - Keep Left: Official Paper of the Young Socialists (London, England), v. 16 no. 9-11, Oct.-Dec. 1967; v. 17-18, 1968-1969; v. 19, Jan.-Sept. 1970, 15.
  - Key List Mailing: Selected Documents of Current and Lasting Interest in the Civil Rights Movement (San Francisco, CA: Bay Area Friends of the Student Nonviolent Committee), June 25, July 9, July 23, 1967, 16.
  - LID News Bulletin (New York, NY: League for Industrial Democracy), v. 5 no. 2, Fall, 1964; v. 6 no. 3/v. 7 no. 1, Fall 1966/Winter 1967, 1. (Box 94)
  - Labor Today (Detroit, MI), v. 6 no. 3, June/July 1967, 2.
  - Labour Research (London, England), v. 58 no. 5, May 1969, 3.
  - Lado (Chicago, IL), v. 1 no. 3-5, April-Aug. 1968, 4.
  - Latin America and Empire Report (New York, NY: North American Congress on Latin America), v. 7 no. 8, Oct. 1973; v. 10 no. 3-10, March-Dec. 1976; v. 11 no. 1, 4, Jan., April 1977, 5.
  - Leaves of Twin Oaks (Louisa, VA), no. 5-16, March 1968-Feb. 1972, 6.
  - Left Speak Out (Peoria, IL), 3 issues, undated, 7.
  - Left Review (Kent, OH), v. 1 no. 1, March 1977, 8.
  - Legislative Reporter (Baltimore, MD), no. 1-9, Jan. 22-May 9, 1969, 9.
  - Letter from China (Peking, China: Anna Louise Strong), no. 49-50, May 30-July 5, 1967; no. 52, Oct. 23, 1967; no. 63-65, Dec. 30, 1968-May 8, 1969; no. 69, Dec. 30, 1969, 10.
  - Leviathan (New York, NY; San Francisco, CA: V. R. Leviathan Publications), v. 1 no. 1-9, March 1969-March 1970; v. 2 no. 1, May 1970, 11.
  - Liberated Guardian (New York, NY: Guardian Workers Collective), April 20, May 1, May 23, June 3, 1970, 12.
  - Liberation (Georgetown, Guyana), v. 1 no. 2, undated, 13.